A Guide to the Department of Confederate Military Records, 1859-1996
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Unit Records
  - Subseries 8: Militia
    - Regiments
      - 129th (5th Division, 27th Brigade)
        - 4th Co. (Avis' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 13)
        - 5th Co. (Carter's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 14)
        - 6th Co. (Buchanan's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 15)
        - 7th Co. (Barsden's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 16)
        - 8th Co. (Wilkinson's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 17)
        - Miscellaneous (See Oversized - Box 7), 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - 132nd (2nd Division, 6th Brigade), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - 135th (5th Division, 19th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Dean's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 20)
        - Co. B (Burr's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 21)
        - Co. C (Reid's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 22)
        - Co. D (Fleshman's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 23)
        - Co. F (Sammons' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 24)
        - Co. I (Humphrey's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - 141st (5th Division, 22nd Brigade), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - 145th (3rd Division, 7th Brigade), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - 149th (3rd Division, 7th Brigade), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - 151st (5th Division, 19th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Caldwell's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 29)
        - Co. B (Scott's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 30)
        - Co. C (Smith's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 31)
        - Co. D (Hall's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 32)
        - Co. E (Massey's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 33)
        - Co. F (Foley's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 34)
        - 155th (2nd Division, 1st Brigade), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 35)
        - 156th (1st Division, 12th Brigade), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - 160th (5th Division, 13th Brigade)
        - Co. F, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - 166th (5th Division, 19th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Haynes' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 38)
        - Co. B (Sanders' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 39)
        - Co. D (Broyles' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 40)
        - Co. E (Arnot's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 41)
        - Co. H (Dunn's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 42)
        - Capt. Ballard's Co. (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 43)
        - Capt. Lively's Co. (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 44)
        - Capt. Taylor's Co. (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - 172nd (1st Division, 11th Brigade), 1865 (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - 179th (4th Division, 2nd Brigade) (1st Regt. 2nd Cl. Militia)
        - Co. A (Danforth's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 17), 1862 (Box 36, Folder 47)
        - Co. B (Allen's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1862 (Box 36, Folder 48)
        - Co. C (Hiltzhimer's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 17), 1862-1907 (Box 36, Folder 49)
        - Co. D (Wilkins' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1862 (Box 36, Folder 50)
        - Co. E (Spencer's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1863-1864 (Box 36, Folder 51)
        - Co. F (Glazebrook's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 17), 1862-1863 (Box 36, Folder 52)
        - Co. G (Lea's Co.) (Mayo's Mounted Guard), 1863 (Box 36, Folder 53)
        - Co. I (Dunkard's Co.), 1913-1922 (Box 36, Folder 54)
        - Co. K (Riddick's Co.), 1912 (Box 36, Folder 55)
        - Miscellaneous, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 56)
      - 184th (5th Division, 27th Brigade), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 57)
      - 187th (5th Division, 27th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Miller's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 58)
        - Co. B (Stollings' Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 59)
        - Miscellaneous (See Oversized - Box 7), 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 60)
      - 188th (3rd Division, 20th Brigade)
        - Co. C (Hankins' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 61)
        - Miscellaneous (See Oversized - Drawer 18), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 62)
      - 190th (5th Division, 27th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Brooks' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 63)
        - Co. B (Bane's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 64)
        - Co. E (Bailey's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 65)
        - Co. F (Coleman's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 66)
        - Co. G (Graham's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 67)
        - Co. H (Blankinship's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 18), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 68)
        - Miscellaneous, 1861 (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Brigades
      - 16th - Field & Staff, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - Subseries 9: Miscellaneous
    - Accomac & Northampton Soldiers (See Oversized - Box 7), n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Ambulance Corps (Army of Northern Virginia), 1912 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Chaplains (Army of Northern Virginia), 1865 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Confederate Cavalry Battalion, 7th
      - Co. A, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Co. B, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Co. D, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Co. E, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Co. F, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Co. H, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Co. I, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Co. K, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Confederate States Navy
      - Miscellaneous, 1905-1915 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Officers, 1884-1907 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Steamers, 1861-1908 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Engineer Corps, 1888-1909 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Engineer Troops - 1st Regiment
      - Co. A, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Co. C, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Co. D (See Also Oversized - Drawer 19), 1864-1910 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Co. E, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Co. F, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Co. G, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Co. H, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Co. I, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Co. K (See Also Oversized - Drawer 19), 1864 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Battalion, 1st, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - German-Americans in Virginia Service, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Hospital Stewards, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Marine Corps (Semmes' Naval Brigade)
      - Co. A, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Co. B, 1914 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Co. C, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Co. E, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Medical Dept. & Hospital Corps, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Non-Virginia Units
      - Georgia
        - 1st Regt. - Co. G (See Oversized - Drawer 19), 1861 (Box 37, Folder 35)
        - 12th Regt. - Co. C (See Oversized - Drawer 19), 1861 (Box 37, Folder 36)
        - 13th Regt. - Co. F (See Oversized - Drawer 19), 1861 (Box 37, Folder 37)
        - Sumter Artillery Bn. (See Also Oversized - Box 7), 1862-1863 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - Louisiana
        - 14th Bn. - Co. A (See Oversized - Drawer 19), 1863 (Box 37, Folder 39)
        - Madison Light Artillery (Madison Tipparary's), n.d. (Box 37, Folder 40)
        - Washington Artillery Battalion (See Also Oversized - Box 7), 1863 (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - Maryland
        - 1st Regt. MD Volunteers, 1861-1862 (Box 37, Folder 42)
        - Baltimore Light Artillery, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - Missouri
        - 1st Regt. MO Cavalry (McNiell's Squadron) - Co. A (Woodson's Co.), n.d. (Box 37, Folder 44)
      - South Carolina
        - 4th Regt. SC Cavalry (See Oversized - Box 7), 1864 (Box 37, Folder 45)
        - 5th Regt. SC Cavalry (See Oversized - Box 7), 1864 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Printer's Guard, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - Public Guard, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Richmond Light Dragoons (Pre-Civil War), n.d. (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Signal Corps, 1911-1913 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Surgeons, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Telegraph Service, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - VMI Corps of Cadets (See Also Oversized - Box 7), 1904-1912 (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Series III: Miscellaneous Records
  Contains certificates issued by the Secretary of Virginia Military Records, certificates issued by the U.S. War Dept., detached muster rolls of unpaid men, Harper's Ferry Rifle Factory records, hospital records, individual service records, John Brown's Raid unit records, Lists of Confederate Soldiers who died in Union Prisons, and other sundry items documenting the work of the Secretary of Virginia Military Records and Dept. of Confederate Military Records.
  The Certificates Issued by the Secretary of Virginia Military Records consist of typescript copies of correspondence certifying the military service records of Confederate veterans between 1910 & 1917. Each certificate provides the name of the veteran along with a brief description of their service including their unit, whether wounded or captured, and dates of enlistment.
  The Certificates Issued by the U.S. War Dept. consist of correspondence from the Secretary of Virginia Military Records between 1912 & 1917 (mostly 1914-1916) to the Adjutant General's Office of the U.S. War Dept. requesting the service records of Confederate veterans for pension applications. On the reverse side of each correspondence are forms issued by the War Dept. summarizing that soldiers' service in the Confederate army (if any information was found). Information included is the name of the soldier, rank, unit, date of enlistment, and the last date found on the company muster roll. Occasionally there is additional information about the soldier's service such as furloughs, discharges, paroles, etc. Each certificate is dated and signed by the Adjutant General.
  The Detached Muster Rolls of Unpaid Men include muster rolls from various regiments during the Civil War. These rolls contain lists of soldiers who did not receive pay. The rolls provide the names and rank of the soldier, length of service, date when they became detached from the regiment, and, in a few cases, the circumstances of the detachment. The rolls are arranged by paymaster. Each paymaster was responsible for the detachments for various units.
  The Harper's Ferry Rifle Factory records contain consolidated abstracts of provisions, payrolls, and powers of attorney from civilian employees working at the Rifle Factory in Harper's Ferry between April and June 1861. The abstracts enumerate and total the number of provisions such as beef, bread, sugar, soap, etc., and the number of men issued these provisions. The powers of attorney were issued by employees to appoint individuals to draw and receive pay on their behalf. Lastly, the payrolls provide the name of the employees who worked at the Rifle Factory, his occupation, days worked, price, total amount, and signature. The payrolls are signed and certified by the Master Armorer, Philip Burkhart, and approved by Brig. Gen. Joseph E. Johnston and Col. Thomas J. Jackson.
  The Hospital Records consist of a register of wounded from Chimborazo Hospital between August & December 1863, a register of wounded from Winchester Hospital between July & August 1864, vouchers for supplies for Chimborazo Hospital from March 1865, and a published article on "The History of Chimborazo Hospital, Richmond Va., and its Medical Officers during 1861-1865" from "The Virginia Medical Semi-Monthly" published in July 1904.
  The Individual Service Records include a small collection of both official and unofficial service records for 70 Confederate veterans gathered by the Adjutant General, the Secretary of Virginia Military Records, and later, the Virginia State Library between 1884 and 1934. Includes correspondence, certificates issued by the U.S. War Dept. and Secretary of Virginia Military Records, affidavits, and personal reminiscences of veterans and their families.
  The John Brown's Raid Unit records contain muster rolls & payrolls from various regiments of the Virginia Militia stationed in Harper's Ferry after John Brown's Raid. There are also powers of attorney containing lists of soldiers' signatures authorizing certain officers to draw pay on their behalf.
  The Lists of Confederate Soldiers who died in Union Prisons include typed lists of Confederate dead compiled by Maj. Joseph V. Bidgood in 1915 for the Department of Confederate Military Records. These lists contain names of Confederate soldiers, their regiment, and burial place transcribed from monuments and headstones. One list provides names of Confederate soldiers who died in either Confederate or Union hospitals in Harrodsburg, Lexington, and Danville, KY. Another list provides the names of Confederate soldiers who died in a railroad accident near Shohola, Pa. The majority of the lists, however, document the deaths of Confederate soldiers in over thirty Union prisons in twelve states. The lists are arranged by Union prison.
  The Miscellaneous (Folders) file includes various lists compiled by the Secretary. These include lists of Confederate veterans at the Gettysburg encampment in 1913, veterans admitted to the Lee Camp Soldiers' Home in 1915, Virginia military organizations mentioned in official war records, and Virginia soldiers mentioned in special orders. There are printed pamphlets containing a roster of the Lee Camp Soldiers' Home in 1913 and also bylaws from 1910. Additional sundry items include acts related to the preservation of Confederate records in Virginia, addresses by Maj. Robert Hunter in 1904 and W. Gordon McCabe in 1908, a draft of Hunter's report to the Governor in 1909, and tabulations (numbers only) of living veterans in 1911.
  The Miscellaneous (Volumes) files contain a number of loose volumes arranged alphabetically by title. Included are registers of officers from various branches of service, local designations, unit data, and other assorted volumes compiled by the Secretary of Virginia Military Records.
  The Scrapbooks include two volumes of clippings from "Our Confederate Column" between 1904 to 1909 and two volumes of obituaries of Confederate veterans who died between 1910 and 1917.
  The Transcripts of General and Special Orders from the Adjutant & Inspector General's Office from 1862 to 1865 were transcribed by the Secretary of Virginia Military Records. The handwritten transcripts of special orders document resignations, appointments, discharges, transfers, leaves of absence, work details, furloughs, and courts of enquiry for Confederate officers and soldiers from Virginia. Special orders No. 1-313 are represented in this collection. These special orders were issued by Jonathan Withers and George Deas, Assistant Adjutant Generals, by the command of the Secretary of War. A few of the orders were also issued directly from Samuel Cooper, Adjutant & Inspector General. The general orders are not as extensive and mostly include resignations and promotions of officers from the Provisional Army of the Confederate States. In addition, general orders numbered 64, 87, and 131 consist of rolls of honor for the battles of Payne's Farm, Chickamauga, Petersburg, and Chancellorsville. Lastly, there are a few miscellaneous transcribed documents including correspondence from John B. Floyd regarding the Battle of Fort Donelson and Jefferson Davis regarding nominations for appointment in the Provisional Army, reports of the Battle of Shiloh by G.T. Beauregard, and other miscellaneous lists of soldiers.
  The Unit Lists contain a few miscellaneous lists compiled by the Secretary of Virginia Military Records. There are lists of infantry battalions, local defense units, militia units, the "Stonewall" Brigade, and unassigned companies. These lists are undated, but were created sometime between 1904 and 1918. There are payrolls from April 1862 for thirty-seven Tidewater Virginia & North Carolina units. These payrolls provide the names of the soldiers and to whom paid. Lastly, there is a catalog of muster rolls from the Richmond Circuit Court related to the court case between the Commonwealth and Joseph F. Wren in 1910. Wren was a rare book dealer who was fighting a court battle against the Secretary of Virginia Military Records for the possession of 200 original muster rolls (See "Clippings, 1884-1922" file).
  The Veterans Lists by County contain miscellaneous lists of veterans and units arranged by county. The lists were collected by the Secretary of Virginia Military Records and compiled by veterans and veteran organizations between 1900 and 1922. Included are newspaper clippings, typescript and handwritten lists, correspondence, and pamphlets. There are two copies of a published "Roster of Warren County Veterans" published by the Warren Memorial Association and Daughters of the Confederacy in 1907. There is another published pamphlet of veterans from Greenbrier County in 1906. The cities of Lynchburg and Portsmouth are also represented in this collection. In addition, there are lists of Virginia veterans from Oklahoma and Kansas City, Missouri, arranged to the rear of the collection.
  - Certificates of Confederate Service Issued by the Secretary of Virginia Military Records
    - A, 1911-1916 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - B, 1911-1917 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - C, 1911-1917 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - D, 1912-1916 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - E, 1911-1916 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - F, 1912-1916 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - G, 1911-1916 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - H, 1911-1917 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - I-J, 1912-1917 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - K-L, 1911-1916 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - M, 1911-1917 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - N-O, 1912-1917 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - P, 1912-1916 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - R, 1910-1916 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - S, 1911-1916 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - T, 1911-1917 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - V-W, 1911-1917 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Y-Z, 1911-1916 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Certificates of Confederate Service Issued by the U.S. War Dept.
    - A, 1914-1917 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - B
      - 1913-1915 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - 1916-1917 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - C
      - 1913-1915 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - 1916-1917 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - D, 1914-1917 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - E, 1914-1917 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - F, 1914-1917 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - G, 1913-1917 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - H
      - 1913-1915 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - 1916-1917 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - I, 1914-1917 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - J, 1914-1917 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - K, 1912-1917 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - L, 1913-1917 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - M
      - 1913-1915 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - 1916-1917 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - N, 1914-1917 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - O, 1914-1917 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - P, 1914-1917 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Q, 1915 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - R, 1913-1917 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - S
      - 1913-1915 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - 1916 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - T, 1914-1917 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - U, 1915 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - V, 1914-1916 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - W
      - 1914-1915 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - 1916-1917 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Y, 1915-1917 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Z, 1915-1917 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Detached Rolls of Unpaid Men (See Oversized - Drawer 20)
  - Harper's Ferry Rifle Factory Records
    - Issues to Troops (See Oversized - Box 8), 1861 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Payrolls
      - 1861 April - June (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
    - Power of Attorney
      - 1861 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Fayetteville, N.C., 1861 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Hospital Records
    - Chimborazo Hospital (Richmond, VA)
      - History by John R. Gildersleeve, 1904 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Register, 1863 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Vouchers for Supplies, 1865 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Winchester Hospital (Winchester, VA)
      - Register, 1864 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Individual Confederate Service Records
    - Agner, Augustus W., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Alcocke, Abner Roane, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Alderson, James M., 1916 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Bacon, William E., 1913 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Beckley, Alfred, 1912 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Beckner, William, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Bolling Family, 1916 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Booker, George, 1922 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Bowe, R. B., 1884 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Boyle, Cornelius, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Breckenridge, P. Gilmer, 1922 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Samuel R., 1913 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Bullington, Henry W., 1912 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Conrad Family, 1908 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Consiris, John W., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Courtney, Giles C., 1904 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Cringan, John, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Davidson, Thomas, 1927 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Deans, Joseph F., 1922 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Denny, Richard S., 1919 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Enroughty, John, 1934 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Fairfax, John W., 1884 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Fulmer, J. A., 1913 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Garnett, James Mercer, 1904 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Gray, Henry V., 1884 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Gunnell, Henry L., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Haw, Joseph R., 1906 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Holsinger, Alexander Jr., 1931 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Horner, J.H., 1913 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Hudgins, R.K., 1884 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Hudson, R.L., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Hunter, John Jr., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Jones, Evan, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Jones, Richard Creed, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Lawson, John & Thomas, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - Leavenworth, Frederick P., 1905 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - Libscomb, J.H., 1920 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - McGuire, Rev. John P., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Mahood, W.M.B., 1921 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Messerschmidt, John (aka Smith, John Mercer), 1933 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Moltz, Henry, 1916 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - Montgomery, Norris, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Nester, Jackson, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - Peters, Osmond, 1884 (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - Read, Thomas Nash, 1922 (Box 45, Folder 45)
    - Redwood, Henry, 1923 (Box 45, Folder 46)
    - Rodgers, A.G. & T.H., 1920 (Box 45, Folder 47)
    - Ruffin, J.C., 1924 (Box 45, Folder 48)
    - Schenck, George, 1913 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - Scott, Frederick R., 1924 (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - Stoakley, William S., 1905 (Box 45, Folder 51)
    - Taylor, James R., 1913 (Box 45, Folder 52)
    - Taylor, S.S. (Emory), 1912 (Box 45, Folder 53)
    - Taylor, Washington, 1892 (Box 45, Folder 54)
    - Turner, Albert C. & George W., 1933 (Box 45, Folder 55)
    - Valentine, Mann S. Jr., 1913 (Box 45, Folder 56)
    - Walker, Henry Harrison, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 57)
    - Warren, Arthur W., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 58)
    - Whitehurst, James D., 1921 (Box 45, Folder 59)
    - Wilburn, Thomas B., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 60)
  - John Brown's Raid Unit Records
    - Artillery
      - 2nd Regiment (Williams' Co.) (Alexandria Artillery) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 1), 1859-1860 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Alburtis's Co. (Wise Artillery) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 1), 1859-1860 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Nichols' Co. (Petersburg Artillery) (See Oversized - Drawer 1), 1859-1860 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Randolph's Co. (Richmond Howitzers) (See Oversized - Drawer 1), 1859-1860 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Sibert's Co. (Tenth Legion) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 1), 1859-1860 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Cavalry